jayasrilanka.net 2019-06-27

# Privacy Policy | JayaSriLanka

#### **JayaSriLanka Privacy Policy**

Fair Information Practices 

Fair information  
Practices

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.  

 **What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**

We do not collect information from visitors of our site.

or other details to help you with your experience.

 **When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you or enter information on our site.

Provide us with feedback on our products or services 

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

 **•** To improve our website in order to better serve you.

 **How do we protect your information?**

We use regular Malware Scanning.

We do not use an SSL certificate

 **•** We only provide articles and information. We never ask for personal or private information like names, email addresses, or credit card numbers.

 **Do we use 'cookies'?**

We do not use cookies for tracking purposes 

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.  

If you turn cookies off, Some of the features that make your site experience more efficient may not function properly.that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.

 **Third-party disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.

 **Third-party links**

We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.

 **Google**

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en 

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.  

 **We have implemented the following:**

 **•** Remarketing with Google AdSense

 **•** Google Display Network Impression Reporting

 **•** Demographics and Interests Reporting

 **•** DoubleClick Platform Integration  

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website. 

**Opting out:**  
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

 **COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.

We market to

We do not collect information from children under 13

children under 13.

Do we let third-parties, including ad networks or plug-ins collect PII from children under 13?

No

 **In order to remove your child's information please contact the following personnel:**

 **We adhere to the following COPPA tenants:**

 **•** Parents can review, delete, manage or refuse with whom their child's information is shared through contacting us directly.

or contacting us directly.  

 **Fair Information Practices**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

 **In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**

We will notify you via email

 **•** Within 7 business days

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

 **CAN SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

 **We collect your email address in order to:**

 **•** Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions

 **To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:**

 **•** Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.

 **•** Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.

 **•** Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.

 **•** Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.

 **•** Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.

 **•** Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

 **  
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at**

 **•** Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.

and we will promptly remove you from **ALL** correspondence.  

 **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may **contact us** using the information below.

jayasrilanka.net

brahmanagoda,weliwatta

ratnapura, sabaragamu 70400 

sri lanka

info@jayasrilanka.net

0094779800085

Last Edited on 2017-10-20

Subscribe Us On Youtube:  

Share This Page On:   

JayaSriLanka.Net is the best place to download or listen Sri Lankan music online. We hope you enjoy our service and stay and find our website valuable. Thank You Very Much For Using This Web Site.

**Follow Us On:**   

Original Song Files Pamanak Upload Karanna,   
Song Eke Music,lyrics,saha wenath thorathuru description thula sadahan karanna.  
artist ge photo ekak aniwaryen ewanna.  
wisthara sadaha 0779800085
